Today is a special day! It's release day of my own Paradise pants.
The Celine Knox limited edition aesthetic pants by Paradise.
Without further ado, I would say I will change into them so you can have a first impression.
Tada! This is the pants! I'm so excited!
Let me first tell you some specifics about the pants itself.
So we have a stipper that's also blue.
But the speciality here is the material because it's a brand new, never in the Paradise product range shown before material.
Can I say it like that? You get what I mean.
because we have a snake pattern texture in the fabric itself and also some kind
of rainbow glitter effect in the color. This is really unique Paradise pants and
the first one with these effects to launch so I'm more than happy about that.
The pants has the trademark curved side seam here like all Paradise pants and this
cool booty cut here which makes a great figure and when I was in Vienna I'm
going to tell you a bit about that soon I learned the original booty pose from
Paradise basically like this Stephanie Pesl herself showed me but yeah I still
have to practice a bit and I just had a look the first Paradise Pants video I
released on my YouTube is three years old. So in October 2020 I showed the
classic aesthetic pants and the ultra aesthetic pants for the first time and
now here we are after this really long and great cooperation. They asked me if I
want to create my own limited edition pants. Yes! So it all started with some
pallets of fabric samples and I had to choose from them like what kind of pens
do I want to do I was a bit overwhelmed at first because so many colors and you
know black was already released haha so I was thinking maybe a dark metal gray
maybe lilac purple maybe blue when I decided on some colors I was allowed to
to order sample pants that were made specifically to my color wishes and I
got three of them because I couldn't really decide and we didn't know what
would look good in the end and it was a process I also said hey can we also
maybe try out something in purple because there's no purple paradise pants
yet except for the metallic lilac and I kind of love purple also metallic ones
or even in combination with bright pink so we tried these as well and let me
just show them to you in general I do love the metallic purple and also the
normal purple but you know with the small color swatches from the sample
cards it's really hard to tell how the pants itself is going to look like if
you have like a lot of fabric so these sample pants are really important and I
still like the color but I didn't see my or the paradise community wearing this
pants so the idea was to have a mixed pants in blue same color PVC and same
color leather look fabric and with the small swatches both fabrics looked like
a great match but again if you see the whole pants you also realize that it
doesn't really 100% match with the colors so I wasn't that satisfied either
even though it is super comfy like this fabric here great comfortability but
yeah the colors I wasn't that happy but then paradise came along and said hey we
got something new snake texture there's also something in blue so this is then
what happened we decided to go with the new fabric and the blue royal blue and
we then made a sample pants surprise of this fabric and you can see it that we
still have a black zipper here and also no paradise plaque in the back no label
so this was the first sample pants and I wanted to work for example because I
wanted to see how does the fabric behave does it stretch enough does it I don't
out here somewhere is it comfortable and it was super comfortable when we all were happy with that
production started and I got to travel to Vienna to meet up with Stephanie and Julia Bessler
to shoot pictures for the home page I had a great time although my camera got stolen from the hotel
but that's a different story if you've been following me on Instagram you heard about that
Anyway, we met up at a photo studio to take the pictures for the homepage.
I got a lot of posing tips for specific pants posing, so to say.
And it was really a cool time there in the studio.
But then we got outdoors because we wanted to do some like street style pictures for social media,
also some videos.
It was really funny because I was always in the middle and I'm obviously a lot taller than Julia and Stephanie
I had so much fun with them outdoors. The weather was not that good at first. It was windy, like really windy
So afterwards we had pizza and we went to the Prater in Vienna which is kind of a constant amusement park
You don't have to pay entry.
And we went there and went on some rides and roller coasters,
which was really fun because they do love roller coasters
as much as I do.
So yes, awesome time.
And the sun came out.
So we had the chance to see this fabric in the sunlight.
And I can tell you, it looks so great
with the rainbow effect outside.
So if you have a chance, go out into the sunlight
and not just an artificial light.
The pants are finally in the Paradise warehouse
and I had to sign like 1000 flyer
that get put into the pant packages.
So if you ever wanted an autograph of me
and I received, yeah, really a few messages
asking for autographs, you just have to order
a Celine Knox Paradise pants to get an autograph.
And yeah, it was a lot to sign.
And I also designed the flyer myself.
So that is something you will find
in every Paradise box with my pants inside.
I had a lot of fun putting it
into some of the setbacks as well.
And having been to the Paradise warehouse
was a cool experience as well.
And I really have to say thank you to Paradise,
to Julia and Stephanie Bessler for doing this with me,
for giving me this opportunity to create these pants
with them together, for the opportunity to work with them
for such a long time,
and it's been an amazing cooperation so far.
I hope we can continue like this,
and I hope you are going to have a lot of fun with my pants.
Send the pictures to me, post them on social media,
tag me in your posts, and enjoy these pants
because I think they're really special.
I really love them,
and I hope you will love them as well.
So click on the link in the description text,
go to the Paradise shop and order them
and also use my discount code for 10% off.
Yeah, I think that's all I have to say today.
I'm probably going to post another video
about the shooting day in Vienna,
so watch out for that if you wanna see more
of the action shots.
And I am wishing you a nice day
and I'll see you in the next video.
Bye!